

# **SOFIA GRYTSENKO**

**CLIFFSIDE PARK, NEW JERSEY** 

### OBJECTIVE

I am searching for a position in the software engineering/user experience field. As a 3.7 GPA Human Centered Computing student at Rochester Institute of Technology, I hope to utilize the skills I have learned to benefit the company. By getting an internship, I look forward to gaining experience in the professional workforce.

### SKILLS

- Java
- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- JavaScript
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe
  Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- SQL

### **EXPERIENCE**

# HORTICULTURAL THERAPY INTERN • NYU LANGONE ORTHOPEDIC HOSPITAL • NEW YORK CITY, NEW YORK • SEPTEMBER 2018 TO MAY 2019

- Shadowed one of the three horticultural therapists.
- Learned how to work with patients, keep meaningful documentation, and how to work with a team.

#### LIFEGUARD • SAF GARD • PARAMUS, NJ • JANUARY 2019 TO AUGUST 2019

- Supervised the pool and provided assistance if needed.
- Learned how to control groups, deal with situations effectively/efficiently, and work under pressure

### **EDUCATION**

#### ROCHESTER INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY • BACHELOR OF SCIENCE • 2023

**Human-Centered Computing Major** 

3.7 GPA

### **PROJECTS**

# UNITY MINIGAME MANIA • SEPTEMBER 2018 - MAY 2019 • HTTPS//GITHUB.COM/SOFGRY19/MINIGAMEMANIA

- Worked with Unity, C#, and SQL to make 3 word-matching minigames
- Learned how to retrieve data from databases and update it.

# NYC TOURIST WEBSITE • 2019-2020 • HTTPS//GITHUB.COM/S0FGRY19/S0FGRY19.GITHUB.I0

 Developed in HTML/CSS for the front-end and JavaScript/PHP/SQL for the back-end

# PHOTOSHOP PROJECTS • 2020 • HTTPS//GITHUB.COM/SOFGRY19/PHOTOSHOPPROJECTS

- A collection of my Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator projects
- Most notably, a recreation of Wassily Kandinsky's Composition VIII made in Adobe Photoshop.



